{
    "hp" : 700,
    "set" : [
        {
            "question": "A school that provides the first part of a child's education, usually for children between five and eleven years old.",
            "answer": ["elementary school"],
            "hint": "2 words, 16 letters (space excluded)"
        },
        {
            "question": "To not do something that you were going to do, or to stop doing something before you have completely finished.",
            "answer": ["drop out"],
            "hint": "2 words, 7 letters (space excluded)"
        },
        {
            "question": "A person whose work is teaching others, or one who is an authority on methods or theories of teaching.",
            "answer": ["educator"],
            "hint": "1 word, 8 letters"
        },
        {
            "question": "Someone who has agreed to work for a skilled person for a particular period of time and often for low payment, in order to learn that person's skills.",
            "answer": ["apprentice"],
            "hint": "1 word, 10 letters"
        },
        {
            "question": "A person's way of thinking and their opinions.",
            "answer": ["mindset"],
            "hint": "1 word, 7 letters"
        },
        {
            "question": "An effect, a reaction, a connection, a response and/or an experience of customers with each other, with a company or with a brand.",
            "answer": ["engagement"],
            "hint": "1 word, 10 letters"
        },
        {
            "question": "An occasion or situation that makes it possible to do something that you want to do or have to do, or the possibility of doing something.",
            "answer": ["opportunity"],
            "hint": "1 word, 11 letter"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not taking help or money from other people.",
            "answer": ["independent"],
            "hint": "1 word, 11 letter"
        },
        {
            "question": "A method of learning where students are given freedom in how, what, when and where they learn.",
            "answer": ["flexible learning"],
            "hint": "2 words, 16 letters"
        },
        {
            "question": "A young person between 13 and 19 years old.",
            "answer": ["Teenager"],
            "hint": "1 word, 8 letters"
        },
        {
            "question": "A piece of planned work or activity that is finished over a period of time and intended to achieve a particular purpose.",
            "answer": ["Project"],
            "hint": "1 word, 7 letters"
        },
        {
            "question": "All the courses given in a school, college,.. or a particular course of study in one subject.",
            "answer": ["curriculum"],
            "hint": "1 word, 10 letters"
        }
    ] 
}